<resources>
    <string name="generate_new_game_title">Generate a new adventure</string>
    <string name="game_generation_placeholder">Enter a theme</string>
    <string name="play_existing_game_title">Return to the familiar</string>
    <string name="congratulations_message"> Congratulations! You have reached the end of the game.</string>
    <string name="blocked_door">This way is blocked. You need an item to proceed.</string>
    <string name="invalid_action_feedback">You can't do that.</string>
    <string name="error_message">Something went wrong. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="reset_game_button">Reset game and exit to menu</string>
    <string name="action_placeholder">Move, pick items or ask questions</string>
    <string name="generating_rooms">Generating rooms</string>
    <string name="creating_puzzles">Creating puzzles</string>
    <string name="just_a_moment">Just a moment</string>
    <string name="locking_chests">Locking chests</string>
    <string name="dropping_keys">Dropping keys</string>
    <string name="almost_there">Almost there</string>
    <string name="hiding_treasures">Hiding treasures</string>
    <string name="placing_traps">Placing traps</string>
    <string name="loading_game">Loading game</string>
    <string name="unveiling_mysteries">Unveiling mysteries</string>

    <!--  Generation rules  -->
    <string name="move_description_rule">Make sure that the directions in which the user can move are mentioned in the description</string>
    <string name="enforce_items_rule">Make sure that items that can be picked up are added to the items list.</string>
    <string name="describing_future_room">When describing the exits in a room, don't specify where they lead.</string>
    <string name="unique_ids_rule">Make sure that all rooms, moves and items have unique ids to the game.</string>

    <!--  Generation prompts  -->
    <string name="generate_game_prompt">Generate a %1$s themed game with the following structure.</string>
    <string name="validate_action_prompt">The user issued the command: %1$s. Determine the action the user wants to take based on the following:
        Move: Check if it matches a valid move from %2$s. If valid, return the move ID with confirmation feedback.
        Pick Up: If not a move, check if the user wants to pick an item from %3$s. If yes, return the item ID with confirmation feedback.
        Invalid: If none of the above, analyze the room description "%4$s" and inventory %5$s and provide some creative feedback for the command.
        Respond with the given structure.
    </string>
    <string name="update_description_prompt">The user has picked up the item %1$s from the room with description %2$s. Update the description such that it does not contain the item anymore. Keep everything else the same.</string>
    <string name="validate_moves_prompt">Update generated game %1$s, such that for each room there is at least one move in the game that leads to that room. Also, update the moves such that for each move from room A to room B, there is a corresponding move from room B to room A in the opposite direction</string>
    <string name="validate_items_prompt">Update the generated game %1$s, such that at least one move in the game has a requiredItem and add this item is in a reachable room. Also, add requiredItems and items otherwise described in the roomDescription which can be picked up are added as itemDTOs in the game structure.</string>
</resources>